regpacks.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy For Regpack Online Registration Software

__

### Privacy Policy of Regpack Inc.

The links below will take you to an overview of our Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy.

You can read the text of each policy, in full, below.

Regpack Inc. collects some Personal Data from its Users.

Owner and Data Controller  
Regpack Inc.

Owner contact email: info@nightlyregpacks.com

**Types of Data collected**  
Among the types of Personal Data that Regpack Inc. collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: email address, first name, last name, phone number, Cookies, Usage Data and Data communicated while using the service.

Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.  
Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using Regpack Inc..  
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by Regpack Inc. is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for Regpack Inc. to provide its services. In cases where Regpack Inc. specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.  
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by Regpack Inc. or by the owners of third-party services used by Regpack Inc. serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available.

Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through Regpack Inc. and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

**Mode and place of processing the Data**  
Methods of processing  
The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of Regpack Inc. (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.

Legal **basis of** processing  
The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:

Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;  
provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;  
processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;  
processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;  
processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.  
In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

**Place**  
The Data is processed at the Owner’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.

Depending on the User’s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User’s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.

Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.

If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.

**Retention time**  
Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for.

Therefore:

Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.  
Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.  
The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.

**The purposes of processing**  
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following purposes: Contacting the User, Analytics, Advertising, Traffic optimization and distribution, Remarketing and behavioral targeting, Managing contacts and sending messages and Interaction with live chat platforms.

Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.

**Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data**  
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

Advertising  
Analytics  
Contacting the User  
Interaction with live chat platforms  
Managing contacts and sending messages  
Remarketing and behavioral targeting  
Traffic optimization and distribution  
Further information about Personal Data  
BlueSnap, Inc.  
WePay  
CardConnect  
Unique device identification  
The rights of Users  
Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner.

In particular, Users have the right to do the following:

Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.  
Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.  
Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.  
Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.  
Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.  
Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.  
Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.  
Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.  
Details about the right to object to processing  
Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.

Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

**How to exercise these rights**  
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

**Cookie Policy**  
Regpack Inc. uses Cookies. To learn more and for a detailed cookie notice, the User may consult the Cookie Policy.

**Additional information about Data collection and processing**  
Legal action  
The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of Regpack Inc. or the related Services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

**Additional information about User’s Personal Data**  
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, Regpack Inc. may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

**System logs and maintenance**  
For operation and maintenance purposes, Regpack Inc. and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with Regpack Inc. (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.

**Information not contained in this policy**  
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

**How “Do Not Track” requests are handled**  
Regpack Inc. does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within Regpack Inc. and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

**Privacy Shield**  
Regpack complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and/or the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework(s), as applicable) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and/or Switzerland, as applicable, to the United States. Regpack has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.

**Cookie Policy of Regpack Inc.**  
Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the Service according to the purposes described. Some of the purposes for which Cookies are installed may also require the User’s consent.

Where the installation of Cookies is based on consent, such consent can be freely withdrawn at any time following the instructions provided in this document.

Technical Cookies and Cookies serving aggregated statistical purposes  
Activity strictly necessary for the functioning of the Service  
Activity regarding the saving of preferences, optimization, and statistics  
Other types of Cookies or third parties that install Cookies  
Some of the services listed below collect statistics in an anonymized and aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner – depending on how they are described – without the help of third parties.

If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information.

Advertising  
Analytics  
Interaction with live chat platforms  
Remarketing and behavioral targeting  
How to provide or withdraw consent to the installation of Cookies  
In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing Cookies.  
Through browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that may have saved the initial consent for the installation of Cookies by this website.  
Users can, for example, find information about how to manage Cookies in the most commonly used browsers at the following addresses: Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Microsoft Internet Explorer.

With regard to Cookies installed by third parties, Users can manage their preferences and withdrawal of their consent by clicking the related opt-out link (if provided), by using the means provided in the third party’s privacy policy, or by contacting the third party.

Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may follow the instructions provided on the subsequently linked initiatives by the EDAA (EU), the Network Advertising Initiative (US) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (US), DAAC (Canada), DDAI (Japan) or other similar services. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.

**Owner and Data Controller**  
Regpack Inc.

Owner contact email: info@nightlyregpacks.com

Since the installation of third-party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within Regpack Inc. cannot be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, the User is kindly requested to consult the privacy policy for the respective third-party services listed in this document.

Given the objective complexity surrounding the identification of technologies based on Cookies, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies by Regpack Inc..
